(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.1",
"generated_at": "2026-07-27T08:27:24.695767",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.1-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
I'm a country girl,
but you're a super city boy
I'm a natural girl,
but you're a prince for me
Everyday wondering how I become your girl
Every night, I'm feeling your body in my dreams
I can't sleep at all,
hello, morning sun
My love, my crush,
wanna tell you my feeling
Please tell me now,
how do you feel me?
I wanna dance with you more
Right now, I want you one for you
Every time, everywhere
I will surely get your honest love
Daisuke
I'm a natural girl, but you're a prince for me
I'm a country girl, but you're a super city boy
Everyday wondering how I become your girl
Every night, I'm feeling your body in my dreams
I can't sleep at all, hello, morning sun
My love, my crush, wanna tell you my feeling
Please tell me now, how do you feel me?
Please show me now, I wanna dance with you more
Right now, I want you one for you
Every time, everywhere
I will surely get your honest love
Daisuke
Please tell me now, how do you feel me?
Please show me now, I wanna dance with you more
Right now, I want you one for you
Every time, everywhere
I will surely get your honest love
Daisuke
Lost hope in love, I thought I'd never understand
Couldn't help it when you took my hand
Roads I ignored before, you left me wanting more
Destroyed everything just to get a bit ahead
Neon lights fly by, is it fake or reality?
Not sure of much, but know I'm ready
Soaring these streets, make me complete
Full throttle, come give me your all
Engine's not keeping up with the beat of my heart
Just can't get enough, revving up, make it fast
Only us, make it last, 'til the sun's up
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end, but we'll
Keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up and don't look back again
Carbonated love
It's better than I coulda dreamed,
Look at what we've done,
we're too extreme.
Pour me your favorite drink,
so much until we sink,
Down to the bottom, don't wanna miss a thing,
Down to the bottom, don't miss a thing,
The track we're on might crash, oh what am I to do?
The track we're on might crash, what am I to do?
Rushing in, ignoring old avenues,
Race through the night, my guiding light,
Sparkling, I'm right here with you.
Engine's not keeping up
With the beat of my heart, just can't get enough
With the beat of my heart, can't get enough
Revving up, make it fast
Only us, make it last
Till the sun's up
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Another shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all ok
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end
But we'll keep on goin' until the bubbles fade
But we'll keep on going until bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Shocking in my heart, give me all you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Time is up, not enough, fill it up and don't look back again
Time is up, not enough, fill it up and look back
Carbonated love
Come overflow my cup, I'm empty without you
Make such a mess of me, don't care if I'm the fool
Another night of bliss, speed up, let's make it new
Love me despite the way I'm crazy just for you
'Nother shot in the dark, take me away
Another shot in the dark, take me away
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all ok
Fizzing up in my heart, it's all okay
Accelerate me until I'm there
You and I reach the line, mark the end
But we'll keep on going until the bubbles fade
I don't care if I don't see another day
Shocking in my heart, give me all that you got
Windows down, don't hesitate a minute more
Love the rush, we shouldn't, don't give up, fire it up again
Love the rush, we shouldn't, don't give up, fire it up
Our time is up, not enough, fill it up and begin
Carbonated love
Hi guys! It's IRyS from Hololive English Promise!
Look at who we have here, aren't they so cute? かわいいっすね、こいつら。
Look at who we have here, aren't they so cute? So cute, these guys.
頑張ってね、踊って、一緒に踊っていただいたんで、うぇい、嬉しい。
They worked hard, danced, and danced along with me, yay, I'm so happy.
And before we, you know, get into all sorts of things, first off, please use the hashtag #IRySBDay2026.
And before we get into all sorts of things, first off, please use the hashtag #IRySBDay2026.
のハッシュタグ是非是非ツイートしてくださいね感想など。If you have anything you want to talk about this live, please use the hashtag.
Please be sure to tweet your impressions with the hashtag. If you want to talk about this live, please use the hashtag.
Have you guys noticed something different? なんか、なんかIRySいつもと見た目違うっしょ？ どう？ Race Queen
Have you guys noticed something different? Doesn't IRyS look different from usual? How is it? Race Queen
あ、興奮してる。あ、で、They look very excited. Yeah, all they're going, they're going mad, yes.
Ah, they're excited. Ah, they look very excited. Yeah, they're going mad, yes.
それぐらい、素晴らしいでしょ？ Finally, the Race Queen outfit is real! Yay!
That's how amazing it is, right? Finally, the Race Queen outfit is real! Yay!
いや、いいね。ありがとうございました。桜じゃないよ！
Man, it's great. Thank you very much. It's not cherry blossoms!
Alrighty then, first off, though, let's get started with introducing the merch, the goods! Yes, here is the lineup this time.
Alrighty then, first off, let's get started with introducing the merch, the goods! Yes, here is the lineup this time.
Birthday Set 4 Merch Acrylic Diorama StandRyS
[Birthday Set: 4 Merch items including Acrylic Diorama StandRyS]
Let me introduce the goods one by one. First off, there's this one.
Acrylic Diorama StandRyS (Acrylic Diorama Stand)
[Acrylic Diorama StandRyS]
From a stand, RyS!
Illustration is by the very, the very best one
in and of Bisuke-sensei's, and こちらの衣装もビスケ先生なんですよ。
in and of Bisuke-sensei's, and this outfit is also by Bisuke-sensei!
The diorama stand features IRyS in her Race Queen outfit, perfectly capturing the atmosphere of this 3D live stage, yes.
Me and Namo... kawaii ne! Yeah! Hi!
Me and Namo... so cute! Yeah! Hi!
And then the second one is this one, yes! The ChibiRyS Tote Bag is so cute!
Illustration as in the... on the tote bag is by LIEN-sensei. So, LIEN-sensei, arigatou, thank you so much LIEN all the time. It's so cute, I love ChibiRyS.
This tote features the mini IRyS in her casual outfit, drawn by LIEN-sensei, so cute!
カジュアルアイリスのね、チビになってますかわいいトート。
A cute tote featuring chibi casual IRyS.
是非普段使いしてください。おでかけで使ってね！
Please use it daily when you go out!
And with the simple design, it's perfect for everyday use. You can pair it with other merch I'll be introducing right after this, so show off your IRyS pride! Yay!
この後に紹介するグッズとも合わして使えるんで楽しみにしててね！はい！
Look forward to using it with the merch coming up next! Yes!
えーっと、and then the third one
Um, and then the third one
is the Race QueenRyS Keychain! こちらの素晴らしいいっしょのキーチェーンになってます、かわいいやろー！
is the Race QueenRyS Keychain! This wonderful keychain together, isn't it cute?!
あ、欲しいの？や、みんなwanted it already! They wanted it already! まじだめ、ここからだよ！
Oh, you want it? Everyone wanted it already! No way, it starts from here!
注文するよね、みんなもう買うよね？
You're gonna order it, right? You guys are gonna buy it, right?
Yeah! Yeah! このセットで、でも終わらないよね？うーん、うーん、もう、もう、爆買いしてくれるそうです！はい！
Yeah! Yeah! With this set, but it doesn't end here, right? Mhm, mhm, they said they're gonna buy it in bulk! Yes!
Um, this is the new plushie featuring my new outfit! 新衣装のアイリスのぬいぐるみキーホルダーになっちゃったよ！
Um, this is the new plushie featuring my new outfit! It became a plushie keychain of IRyS's new outfit!
It's definitely cute on its own, but you can also carry it with its face peeking out from the outer pocket of the tote bag!
トートバッグの中にポーンって入れちゃって一緒にやお出かけしてね！はい！
Pop it inside the tote bag and go out together! Yes!
And then the last one is the...
YabaiRyS Pouch! 皆の大好きなヤバイリスだよ！何を考えてるんでしょ、I wonder what she's with that face of hers, yes!
YabaiRyS Pouch! Everyone's favorite YabaiRyS! I wonder what she's thinking with that face of hers, yes!
Is ba-, YabaiRyS is back again! This face pouch with its high-impact design, yes, it's high-impact.
Can also be attached to the bag handle! さっき紹介したトートバッグの取っ手にポーンってつけるととってもかわいいよ！
Can also be attached to the bag handle! Pop it onto the handle of the tote bag I introduced earlier, and it's super cute!
Yes, you can use it with the tote bag. Just put it on the tote bag, and it'll be a perfect set. Tote and the pouch as a three-piece set, you can show off your IRyS love all around the world! Yes!
あ、ちなみにこれはポーチだからね。Just just clarifying. こればポーチになってます。You can zip it open and put things in it, tiny things in it. Yay!
Oh, by the way, this is a pouch, just clarifying. It's a pouch. You can zip it open and put things in it, tiny things in it. Yay!
And then here are the full set bonuses! Yes, the postcard!
Illustration is the same illustration from Bisuke-sensei for the acrylic stand in Bisuke-sensei no 素晴らしいラストは、こちらのポストカードでも使ってます！
Illustration is the same illustration from Bisuke-sensei for the acrylic stand, and Bisuke-sensei's wonderful illustration is also used for this postcard!
The limited edition features a handwritten message!
ええと、数量限定版は直筆メッセージ＆箔押し複製サイン入りあ、メッセ、箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードです！
Um, the limited edition features a handwritten message & foil-stamped duplicate autographed postcard!
The standard version comes with a foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message as well, and 直筆、直筆はメッセージの方です。So you could get both! ね、あのぜひ限定版も通常版もぜひゲットしてね！
The standard version comes with a foil-stamped duplicate autograph and message as well, and the handwritten one is for the message. So you could get both! Be sure to get both the limited and standard versions!
ね、あの限定版も通常版もぜひゲットしてね！みんなかわいいな、you guys are so cute. They're so cute, look at how big their heads are! 頭でっかいね、あ、刺される！あ、痛いよ、痛い！痛いよ！
Be sure to get both the limited and standard versions! You guys are so cute. They're so cute, look at how big their heads are! Their heads are so big, ah, I'm gonna get stabbed! Ow, it hurts, it hurts, it hurts!
もう君たちはしょうがないな。There are plenty more announcements coming up! If you guys keep time ready introducing merch, there's a lot of other things coming up. この後もね、いろんな大きな告知があるんで、ぜひ最後まで見ててね、楽しみにしててね！
You guys can't be helped. There are plenty more announcements coming up! If you guys keep time ready introducing merch, there's a lot of other things coming up. There are lots of big announcements coming up after this, so please stay tuned until the end and look forward to it!
There's still big announcements after this, so stay tuned! じゃ、続きやるぞ！Let's go on with the live!
There's still big announcements after this, so stay tuned! Now, let's continue! Let's go on with the live!
うーん...
Ooh...
まるで この 世界 で ふたり だけ みたい だね
It seemed to me that we are the only people in this world,
なんて 少し だけ 夢 を 見て しまった だけ
but it turned out that I just fell asleep for a moment.
爪先 に 月明かり 花束 の 香り 指 に 触れる 指
Moonlight on my toes, the scent of a bouquet of flowers, a finger touching a finger,
さよなら もう 行かなくちゃ 何もかも 忘れて
goodbye, I must go, forget everything.
硝子 の 上 を 裸足 の まま 歩く
I'm walking barefoot on the glass.
痛む ごとに 血 が 流れて 落ちていく
With each painful step, drops of blood drip from my feet.
お願い その 赤い 足跡 を 辿って 会いにきて
I beg you, follow these red footprints and come to me.
錆びた プール に 放たれていく 金魚
A goldfish released into a rusty pool,
靴箱 の 中 隠した 林檎
an apple hidden in a shoe cabinet,
萎びた 君 の 肌 に 残る 傷跡
scars left on your withered skin,
犬 の ように 泳いだ 迷子
a lost child swimming like a dog.
どこに いる の （ ここ に いる よ ）
Where are you? (I'm here)
何 を して いる の （ ずっと 見てる よ ）
What are you doing? (I've been watching all this time)
この 世 を 間違い で 満たそう
Let's fill this world with mistakes.
側 に いて よ 遊び に 行こう よ
Stay by my side, let's go play.
どこに いる の
Where are you?
この 世 は 間違い で 満たそう
Let's fill this world with mistakes.
硝子 の 上 を 裸足 の まま 歩く
I'm walking barefoot on the glass.
痛む ごとに 血 が 流れて 落ちていく
With each painful step, drops of blood drip from my feet.
お願い その 赤い 足跡 を 辿って 会いにきて
I beg you, follow these red footprints and come to me.
まるで この 世界 で
It seemed to me
ふたり だけ みたい だね
that we are the only people in this world,
なんて 少し だけ 夢 を 見て しまった だけ
but it turned out that I just fell asleep for a moment.
揺らし 一秒 駆けたら summer girls
Shake it — one second, sprint and we're summer girls
夢 へ の 道 は ストレート
The path to our dreams is straight ahead
視線 誰に も 譲れない
My eyes won't give way to anyone
Please, Gaze on Me! きっと 始まる Fantastic time
Please — gaze on me! Surely, a fantastic time's about to start
（ ゴール は Spot light ）
(The finish is the spotlight)
（ I'm the heroine ）
(I'm the heroine)
（ Please, Gaze on Me! Fantastic time ）
(Please — gaze on me! Fantastic time)
みんな 準備 は いい です か ？ Burning
Everyone — you ready? Burning up
うなずいて 陽炎 も Heat up
Nod along — even the heat shimmer's turning hot
どうしよう 上昇 あがる 空気
Oh my — the vibe's rising, we're getting hyped
Let's go!
さあ太陽燃えて最高
Now, let the sun burn at its peak!
mate 負けられない
Mate, I won't lose,
興奮もハートも
neither my excitement nor my heart.
掛け引きは no no
Playing games? No, no.
gate 開いたなら
Once the gate opens,
一瞬のドラマ
it's a momentary drama.
走れ夏の方へ！
Run toward the summer!
揺らせ一秒駈け出したら summer girls
With one second to shake, when I dash, summer girls,
夢への道はストレート
the road to dreams is a straight line.
視線誰にも譲れない
I won't yield my gaze to anyone.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる fantastic time
A fantastic time is surely beginning.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
ゴールは spot light
The goal is the spotlight.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
I'm the heroine
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
キミを頂戴
I want you.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる fantastic time
A fantastic time is surely beginning.
絶対最上掴みたい feeling
Wanting to grasp the absolute best feeling,
全身全霊めぐるから get hot
body and soul revolve, so get hot.
テンション高揚欲しいモノへ
With high tension, toward what I desire,
今 ride on time 乗って it's show time
now ride on time, hop on, it's show time.
peak 迎えるとき遠慮はいらない
When meeting the peak, no hesitation is needed.
せめぎあい oh oh
Jostling, oh oh,
spark 汗とプライド
spark, sweat and pride,
ジレた運命
irritated fate.
連れて夏の方へ！
Take me toward the summer!
挑む世界は魅惑の sunlight floor
The world we challenge is a fascinating sunlight floor.
天井知らずのボルテージ
Voltage with no ceiling,
火照る季節をモノにして
making the flushed season our own.
Please, Gaze on Me!
クラリさせたい exciting time
An exciting time to make you dizzy.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
ゴールは spot light
The goal is the spotlight.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
I'm the heroine
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
キミを頂戴
I want you.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる fantastic time
A fantastic time is surely beginning.
関係ないどんな私だって
No matter what kind of person I am,
真夏駈け出せたら venus
if I dash out in midsummer, I'm a Venus.
アツくなれば一歩で change & happy
Becoming passionate in one step, change & happy.
眩しすぎる今日を
This hard-to-bear dazzling day,
踊るように手にしよう
let's take it in hand as if dancing.
さぁ here we go!
Now, here we go!
ビートは止まらない
The beat won't stop.
keep 思うままに身を預けて
Keep, entrusting yourself as you wish,
灼熱へ go go
go go toward the scorching heat.
warp 本能のリズム
Warp, the rhythm of instinct,
打ち鳴らして
beating it out,
走れ夏の方へ！
run toward the summer!
揺らせ一秒駈け出したら summer girls
With one second to shake, when I dash, summer girls,
夢への道はストレート
the road to dreams is a straight line.
視線誰にも譲れない
I won't yield my gaze to anyone.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる fantastic time
A fantastic time is surely beginning.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
ゴールは spot light
The goal is the spotlight.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
I'm the heroine
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
キミを頂戴
I want you.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる fantastic time
A fantastic time is surely beginning.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
ゴールは spot light
The goal is the spotlight.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
I'm the heroine
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
キミを頂戴
I want you.
Please, Gaze on Me!
クラリさせたい exciting time
An exciting time to make you dizzy.
関係ないどんな私だって
No matter what kind of person I am,
真夏駈け出せたら venus
if I dash out in midsummer, I'm a Venus.
アツくなれば一歩で change & happy
Becoming passionate in one step, change & happy.
眩しすぎる今日を
This hard-to-bear dazzling day,
踊るように手にしよう
let's take it in hand as if dancing.
さぁ here we go!
Now, here we go!
ビートは止まらない
The beat won't stop.
keep 思うままに身を預けて
Keep, entrusting yourself as you wish,
灼熱へ go go
go go toward the scorching heat.
warp 本能のリズム
Warp, the rhythm of instinct,
打ち鳴らして
beating it out,
走れ夏の方へ！
run toward the summer!
keep 思うままに身を預けて
Keep, entrusting yourself as you wish,
灼熱へ go go
go go toward the scorching heat.
warp 本能のリズム
Warp, the rhythm of instinct,
打ち鳴らして
beating it out,
走れ夏の方へ！
run toward the summer!
揺らせ一秒駈け出したら summer girls
With one second to shake, when I dash, summer girls,
夢への道はストレート
the road to dreams is a straight line.
視線誰にも譲れない
I won't yield my gaze to anyone.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる fantastic time
A fantastic time is surely beginning.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
ゴールは spot light
The goal is the spotlight.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
I'm the heroine
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
キミを頂戴
I want you.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる fantastic time
A fantastic time is surely beginning.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
ゴールは spot light
The goal is the spotlight.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
I'm the heroine
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
キミを頂戴
I want you.
Please, Gaze on Me!
クラリさせたい exciting time
An exciting time to make you dizzy.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
ゴールは spot light
The goal is the spotlight.
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
I'm the heroine
(la la la la la la...)
(La, la, la, la, la...)
キミを頂戴
I want you.
Please, Gaze on Me!
きっと始まる fantastic time
A fantastic time is surely beginning.
教えて！もっとあなたの事
Tell me more about you!
聞かせて！もっとあなたの声
Let me hear more of your voice!
こんなドキドキもう抑え切れない
This pounding heart can't be contained anymore!
友達は卒業 運命の私見つけて欲しいの
Graduating from friends, I want you to find your destined me!
one 勇気を出して
One, gather your courage;
two 見つめる作戦
two, the staring strategy;
three 瞳と目が合えば
three, if our eyes meet;
fall 止められない
fall, I can't stop!
yeah yeah yeah この恋この愛で
Yeah, yeah, yeah, with this love and affection,
melt melty 溶けちゃうよ
melt, melty, I'll melt away!
ねえ？ねえ？ねえ？気付いて my darling
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice me, my darling!
届け！大好き！
Reach him! I love you!
アイ愛、スクリ～ム scream 呼びましょ
Ai, love, scream! Let's shout it out!
(スクリーム！アイスクリーム！)
(Scream! Ice cream!)
OK！
OK!
アイ愛、スクリ～ム scream 呼びましょ
Ai, love, scream! Let's shout it out!
(スクリーム！アイスクリーム！)
(Scream! Ice cream!)
ルビィちゃん！ 「はーい」 何が好き ？
Mio-chan! "Yes!" What do you like?
チョコミント より も あ ・ な ・ た
Even more than chocolate mint... you!
歩夢ちゃん！ 「はーい」 何が好き ？
IRyS-chan! "Yes!" What do you like?
ストロベリー フレーバー より も あ ・ な ・ た
Even more than strawberry flavor... you!
四季ちゃん！ 「はーい」 何が好き ？
Fubu-chan! "Yes!" What do you like?
クッキー ＆ クリーム より も あ ・ な ・ た
Even more than cookies & cream... you!
みんな 「 はーい 」 何 が 好き ？
Everyone! "Yes!" What do you like?
モチロン 大好き aiscream
Of course, I love aiscream!
止め られ ない
Can't stop!
yeah yeah yeah この 恋 この 愛 で
Yeah, yeah, yeah, with this love and affection,
melt melty 溶け ちゃう よ
melt, melty, I'll melt away!
ねえ ？ ねえ ？ ねえ ？ 気づい て my darling
Hey? Hey? Hey? Notice me, my darling!
届け ！ 大好き ！
Reach him! I love you!
アイ 愛 、 スクリ ～ ム scream 呼び ましょ
Ai, love, scream! Let's shout it out!
(スクリーム ！ アイスクリーム ！)
(Scream! Ice cream!)
ok ！
OK!
アイ 愛 、 スクリ ～ ム scream 呼び ましょ
Ai, love, scream! Let's shout it out!
(スクリーム ！ アイスクリーム ！)
(Scream! Ice cream!)
アイ♡スクリーム！
Ai-Scream!
教えて！もっとあなたの事
Tell me! More about you
聞かせて！もっとあなたの声
Let me hear! More of your voice
この心は止まらない
This heart's racing, can't hold it inside
Friends are past, it's fate, 大好き！
Friends are past, it's fate, I love you!
One, 勇気を出して
One, gather up my courage
Two, 近づく作戦
Two, lock eyes with a plan
Three, 手と手が触れて
Three, our gazes collide
Fall, 止まらない！
Fall, I'm falling!
止められない
Can't stop, no way!
YEAH YEAH YEAH この恋この愛で
YEAH YEAH YEAH, with this love, this fire
MELT MELTY 溶けちゃうよ
MELT MELTY, I'm melting away
ねぇ、ねぇ、ねぇ、気づいて my darling
Hey, hey, hey, won't you see, my darling?
届け！大好き！
Reach you, I love you!
アイ♡スクリーム、叫びましょ
Love, scream, let's scream it out loud!
スクリーム！アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
アイ♡スクリーム、叫びましょ
Love, scream, let's scream it out loud!
スクリーム！アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
おねがい見つけて my darling
Please find me, my darling
おねがい気づいて my darling
Please see me, my darling
One, 勇気を出して
One, gather up my courage
Two, 近づく作戦
Two, get closer, my plan
Three, 手と手が触れて
Three, our hands brush, oh my
Fall 溶けちゃうよ
Fall, I'm falling!
止められない
Can't stop, no way!
YEAH YEAH YEAH この恋この愛で
YEAH YEAH YEAH, with this love, this fire
MELT MELTY 溶けちゃうよ
MELT MELTY, I'm melting away
ねぇ、ねぇ、ねぇ、気づいて my darling
Hey, hey, hey, won't you see, my darling?
それは！アナタ！
It's you, my only one!
アイ♡スクリーム、叫びましょ
Love, scream, let's scream it out loud!
スクリーム！アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
アイ♡スクリーム、叫びましょ
Love, scream, let's scream it out loud!
スクリーム！アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
アイ♡スクリーム、叫びましょ
Love, scream, let's scream it out loud!
スクリーム！アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
アイ♡スクリーム、叫びましょ
Love, scream, let's scream it out loud!
スクリーム！アイスクリーム！
Scream! Ice cream!
La-la-la-la-la, love, love
La-la-la-la-la, love, love...
ねぇあたし知ってるよ きみがひとり涙してるの
Hey, guess what, I know that you're alone and crying
知ってるよ ピクンピクン震えてさ 声もダダ漏れなんだわ
I know it, twitching and trembling, your voice is leaking out
正直に言っちゃえば バレてんだし言っちゃえば 聞いてんの？
To be honest, if you're exposed, just spill it, are you listening?
普通普通 平気だよ みんな分かってないだけ
It's totally fine, everyone just doesn't get it
もしもし…ねぇ大丈夫？ねぇ心配だから 今からそっち行くね
Hello? Hey, are you alright? I'm getting worried, I'm coming over
ねぇあたし知ってるよ きみがひとり涙してるの
Hey, guess what, I know that you're alone and crying
知ってるよ グスングスン凹んでさ 弱音ヒトカラいいんじゃない？
I know it, sobbing and depressed, solo karaoke isn't bad, right?
朝が来るまで一緒トーク もっと泣いたって 何度だって受け止めてあげる もう我慢しないでいっぱい吐いてね
Let's talk all night 'til dawn, cry all you want, I'll embrace you again and again, don't hold back, spill it all!
Mwah! お願いきみが欲しいの 慰めさせてベストフレンド 愛の才能で
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad. Let me comfort you, best friend, with my knack for love!
泣いてくれるかい きみの辛い 抱き締めたい ねぇいいでしょ？
Will you cry? Your pain, I want to hold tight. Hey, is that okay?
分け合って乗り越えたい 戦ったってば
Let's share and overcome it together!
Mwah! お願いきみが欲しいの 笑い飛ばしてホップステップジャンプ さあ行こうぜ
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad. Laugh it off, hop, step, jump, let's go!
分けてくれるかい きみに思い ぶらんよ思いでいいでしょ 寄り添って救いたいんだってば
Will you share your feelings with me? Leaning close, I want to save you!
見たい見たい見たい見たい… きみの中
Let me see, let me see... inside of you
ねぇあたし知ってるよ きみがひとり悔しがってんの
Hey, guess what, I know that you're all alone vexing
知ってるよ グスングスン終わるまで きみを決して諦めない
I know it, until your sobs subside, I'll never give up on you
ねぇあたし知ってるよ きみはできる子知ってるよ
Hey, guess what, I know you're fully capable
つらい時は弱いぐらいでちょうどいい あたしきみの味方だよ
When it's tough, weakness is just right, I'm on your side
Mwah! お願いきみが欲しいの 名前を呼んでよいつだって会いに参上
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad. Call my name, I'll come to see you anytime!
きみはひとりか それは違う ひとりじゃないもういいでしょ ソロプレイはお仕舞いなんだってば
You think you're alone? That's not true, solo play is finished!
きみがどんな時もあたし側柄いるわ いつも見守っているわ そうよ怖くないのよ
No matter when, I'm by your side, always watching over you, don't be scared!
Mwah! お願いきみが欲しいの 慰めさせて…
Mwah! Please, I want you so bad. Let me comfort you...
慰めさせてベストフレンド
Let me comfort you, my best friend,
愛の才能で 泣いてくれるかい？
will you cry for me with your talent for love?
きみのツライ 抱きしめたい ねぇいいでしょう？
I want to embrace your pain, is that okay?
分け合って 乗り越えたいんだだってば
I want us to share it and overcome it, really!
お願いキミが欲しいの 笑い飛ばしてホップ・ステップ・ジャンプ最高ぜ
Please, I want you! Laugh it off with a hop, step, and jump, it's the best!
分け合ってくれるかい？ キミの想い 黒い想い 覗きたい
Will you share it with me? Your feelings, your dark feelings, I want to peek inside.
吸い取りって救いたいんだだってば
I want to absorb it and save you, really!
ねぇアタシ知ってるよ キミがひとりで秘密抱えてるの 知ってるよ
Hey, I know you're keeping secrets all by yourself, I know.
グズグズ凹んでないで 弱音吐いたっていいんじゃない？
Don't mope around sluggishly, isn't it okay to vent your weakness?
ずっと一緒もっと泣いたって 何度だって受け止めてあげる
We'll be together forever, even if we cry more, I'll accept you no matter how many times.
問題のうしろで 出してってば
Behind the trouble, let it out, I tell you!
GO BEAT CRAZY
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Beat, beat, baby
Music gets you crazy
Shock me tonight
Go beat crazy!
Fun, fun, baby
Dancin' feelin' hazy
Shake out of sight
Go beat crazy!
And you will spin in a trance
No lovely dovey romance
If you wanna go crazy
Keep on movin' your body 'round
I just wanna feel you go mad!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Boom, boom, baby
Come and shake your booty
Dig it tonight
Go beat crazy!
Go, go, baby
Show me that you're ready
Get satisfied
Go beat crazy!
And you will spin in a trance
No lovely dovey romance
If you wanna go crazy
Keep on movin' your body 'round
I just wanna feel you go mad!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Beat, beat, baby
Fun, fun, baby
Go beat crazy!
Boom, boom, baby
Go, go, baby
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Keep on movin' your body round
I just wanna feel you go mad
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Everybody dance
Everybody groove
Everybody go
Go beat crazy!
Step into the dance
Get into the groove
And let the party go
Go beat crazy!
Are you ready?
Everybody make some noise
誰も真似できやしないな
Nobody can copy the formula
スターのガイダンス
Star-led guidance charisma
バズりまくり 常にテクニカルに
Trending, we're makin' it, always tactical
ヘイターたちにご提案 ディスるより Do what you love
Haters, I gotta tell ya, do what you love
朝から晩まで Ring a ring a ling
All day long, let it ring a ring a ling
勝ちや負け気にすの論外 ミスるの問題とか言ってんのが大問題
Win or lose? Not the problem. 'A minor mistake'—that's the real problem!
Alright 自分 が正解
Alright, I'm gonna define
everyone 必ず信念を貫く
Everyone push ahead with strong heart
We are! We are! No. 1
CHARISMAX 最強のマインド
Charismax, the one and only mind
CHARISMAX 時代塗り替える
Charismax, now rewrite the age
CHARISMAX 世界が驚く どいつもこいつも Crazy crazy man
Charismax, we gon' gasp the world, everyone is crazy crazy man
CHARISMAX 常識壊してゆく
Much beyond the common sense
CHARISMAX まるで人生はステージみたいだ
Don't you see life's like a stage
皆が役者 CHARISMAX
Doing a role-play charisma
何でもできる そう 君は何でもできる
You can do anything, right?
CHARISMAX wanna beたちにご提案
Wannabes, I gotta tell ya
今すぐに Do what you want
Do what you want, charisma
世界に響かせる Ding a ding a ling
Sing along, let's get it, ding a ding a ling
空気は読むより変えていく Style
Let me change it all, it's my style
はみ出す天才
Sticking out genius
てか愛想笑いなんてしない
No fake smiles, make it right
Alright 答えは明快
Alright, answer's generous
everyone 必ず信念を貫く
Everyone push ahead with strong heart
We are! We are! No. 1
CHARISMAX 才能解き放つ
Charismax, the talent's not an imitation
CHARISMAX 進化をし続ける
Charismax, unstoppable evolution
CHARISMAX 限界越えてゆく
Charismax, go beyond the limitation
CHARISMAX どいつもこいつも Crazy crazy woman
Charismax, everyone is crazy crazy woman
everyone 必ず信念を貫く
Everyone push ahead with strong heart
We are! We are! No. 1
CHARISMAX 最強のマインド
Charismax, the one and only mind
CHARISMAX 時代塗り替える
Charismax, now rewrite the age
CHARISMAX 世界が驚く
Charismax, we gon' gasp the world
CHARISMAX どいつもこいつも Crazy crazy man
Better watch us, everyone is crazy crazy man
CHARISMAX 才能解き放つ
Charismax, the talent's not an imitation
CHARISMAX 進化をし続ける
Charismax, unstoppable evolution
CHARISMAX 限界越えてゆく
Charismax, go beyond the limitation
CHARISMAX どいつもこいつも Crazy crazy woman
Charismax, everyone is crazy crazy woman
FOCUS
Can I get, get, get all your attention
I bet you don't know me yet
君の奥底まで 穿つ目線で
Piercing straight to your core with my gaze
溢れる様 IQ ammo 獲る天下
Overflowing IQ ammo, taking the world
A catalyst, I know. And I say go. Put your hands up
混沌の最中に 降臨した女神
A goddess descended in the midst of chaos
I feel it up, got it ice cold on my body
You wanna know, but you don't 震感させる異能
You wanna know, but you don't—a chilling ability
I'm a go, I'm a shine, shine, shine, shine
Can't stop, gotta make my fantasy
Now you see
星空を 飲み込まんだ 私に
Swallowing the starry sky into me
Hidden deep within my universe come find me now
Hear the voice that's calling out
まだ見ぬ世界の真髄を見せてあげるから
I'll show you the true essence of an unseen world
Baby, for now, calm down, let me focus
Under my spell like a nosis, so don't get too close when I'm
Under my spell like a gnosis, so don't get too close when I'm
Come-a, come-a, come in through You wanna roll with me
Come, come, come in through, you wanna roll with me
Come-a, come-a, come in through We take 'em down, yes
Come, come, come in through, we take 'em down, yes
I tell you what to do I got nothing to prove Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do 脳髄までbulletproof Cold when I do, when I do, when I focus
I tell you what to do, bulletproof to the brain, cold when I do, when I do, when I focus
On me Back at my best, I finesse
私の脳裏に潜む怪物は no secret
The monster lurking in my mind is no secret
冷静に cool, my attitude
Calm and cool, my attitude
Target in my sight locked in, ready to shoot, like
Mayday, this is an emergency Working under pressure, baby, I can do this in my sleep
世の理だって書き換えてしまうようなノゾノ
Rewriting even the laws of the world
When I go, when I go, I'm a shine, shine, shine, shine
Can't stop, gotta make my fantasy
Now you see
銀河を ネオンを 外どろがすように
Like shaking galaxies and neon lights
Hidden deep within my universe come find me now
Clear my mind of all these doubts
まだ見ぬ世界の真髄 この目で 見たいから
I want to see the unseen world's true essence with my own eyes
Baby, for now, calm down, let me focus
Under my spell like a nosis, so don't get too close when I'm
Under my spell like a gnosis, so don't get too close when I'm
Come-a, come-a, come in through You wanna roll with me
Come, come, come in through, you wanna roll with me
Come-a, come-a, come in through We take 'em down, yes
Come, come, come in through, we take 'em down, yes
I tell you what to do I got nothing to prove Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do 脳髄までbulletproof Cold when I do, when I do, when I focus
I tell you what to do, bulletproof to the brain, cold when I do, when I do, when I focus
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, ohh
垂れろ頭 don't break my focus
Bow your head, don't break my focus
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, ohh Wanna try and play catch up? Follow my mind
I'm a get you talkin' about it loud Can't get rid of me now
I'mma get you talkin' about it loud, can't get rid of me now
唯一無二 so I'm crowned Put my feet on the ground
One and only, so I'm crowned, put my feet on the ground
任されたくわ As piece of cake, it's no stress
Leaving it to me as piece of cake, it's no stress
銀河中を魅了して What's next? Take a guess
Mesmerizing the galaxy, what's next? Take a guess
I tell you what to do I got nothing to prove Cold when I move, when I move, when I focus
I tell you what to do 脳髄までbulletproof Cold when I do, when I do, when I focus
I tell you what to do, bulletproof to the brain, cold when I do, when I do, when I focus
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, ohh
垂れろ頭 don't break my focus
Bow your head, don't break my focus
O-ma, o-ma, o-ma, ohh Wanna try and play catch up? Follow my mind
The time has come to pack away
all the joys
You don't wanna hear my apology
Get it off my chest, I would do my best
I know what you fear, similarities
we possess
Never will I pass the test
The scene is fading, can my soul be put to rest?
Death is gonna come for me, be the change I couldn't be
Can you find a life that's like fairy tales, far from this tragedy
Sad you had to wait for me, feels like an eternity
Please forgive me for my sins, angels wings lifting and setting me free
Death is gonna come for me, be the change I couldn't be
Can you find a life that's like fairy tales, far from this tragedy
Sad you had to wait for me, feels like an eternity
Please forgive me for my sins, angels wings lifting and setting me free
The question of my love
Slipping right through the cracks
and crumbling to dust
The question of my love
Slipping right through the cracks
and crumbling to dust
Oh, we're getting toward the end of the live.
There are still many beautiful songs and so many beautiful guests.
I love the glasses, the Katsumax and Daisuke glasses, good stuff.
And we're getting to the end, which means... announcements! Yeah!
ええと、このあともね、あのメンゲンパートもあるので、ぜひメンバーシップに入ってこい！
Um, there will also be a members-only part after this, so please join the membership!
えっと、この後もね、あの、メインゲームパートもあるので、ぜひメンバーに、メンバーシップに入ってこい！イエーイ！
There's also a main game part after this, so definitely join the membership! Yay!
歌も歌うんでね。Yes.
And I'll sing a song too. Yes.
ああ、オッケー, then! Are you guys ready for the announcement?
Ah, okay then! Are you guys ready for the announcement?
すっごくすっごく嬉しい告知があります！ It's a big, big announcement, I'm really, really happy about it. I can't wait, I'm super happy I get to share with you guys.
I have a super, super happy announcement! It's a big announcement I'm really happy about.
嬉しい告知、行きます！まずは、こちらをご覧ください！ Please watch this short video.
Here comes the happy announcement! First, please watch this short video!
願いを叶える魔法があるとするなら
Should there be a spell that could grant my wishes
それは、あなた。
It would be you
2026 Oct 6th JAPAN TOKYO
IRyS 1st Concert
VENUE SGC HALL ARIAKE
そしてわたしは、あなたに贈る
And I will gift you with
奇跡で出来た、この希望を。
Hope made of miracles.
ついに、ことしで！ Yes! IRyS, I will be having my very first solo live!
Finally, this year! Yes! I will be having my very first solo live!
in Tokyo, Japan! アイリスの初めてのソロライブ、日本で開催されることが決定しました！わー！
in Tokyo, Japan! IRyS's very first solo live has been decided to be held in Japan! Woo!
Yes! It will be in Tokyo at the SGC Hall Ariake! えっと場所は東京のSGCホール有明でございます！
Yes! It will be in Tokyo at the SGC Hall Ariake!
日程は10月6日 It's going to be on a Tuesday, 10月6日火曜日でございます！ It'll be happening on October 6th, Tuesday! Yeah! マイカレンダーに！
The date is October 6th, Tuesday! Yeah! Mark your calendars!
ずっとね、本当に夢に見ていたステージに立てることがすごく嬉しく思いますし、本当にみんなの応援のおかげです、ありがとうございます！
I'm so happy to stand on a stage I've dreamed of, and it's thanks to everyone's support!
It's all thanks to your guys' support that I get to have this opportunity, so thank you so much! がんばるぞー！ Yay!
It's all thanks to your support! Let's do our best! Yay!
えっとね、I'm working really hard to make this live an amazing one for you guys, a very magical one.
I'm working really hard to make this live an amazing one for you guys.
So please look forward to it, make sure you definitely come! If you don't come, I'll be sad. If you don't come, you'll also regret it! Yes!
So please come! If you don't come, I'll be sad and you'll regret it!
あのライブに向けて準備めちゃくちゃ頑張ってるんで、素晴らしいライブになるように頑張ってるんで、ぜひ会場に見に来てください！見に行かないとアイリス悲しいし、みんなも後悔するぞ！
I'm working hard on preparations, so please come to the venue!
そして、and along with it! Yes, I will also be releasing my very first full album!
And along with it! Yes, I will also be releasing my very first full album!
なんと、アイリス初のフルアルバム出ます！そう、なんだかんだってね、今までEPだったんですけど、フルアルバムは初めてです！
IRyS's very first full album! Up until now it's been EPs, but this is a full album.
Yeah, I've released EPs in the past, but this is the very first full album! So look forward to it, there's a lot of songs, the album jacket...
So look forward to it, there's a lot of songs in the album jacket...
え、これ見せれる？ Yeah, album jacket is by kid and Koruta sensei's... It's very cute!
Oh, the album jacket is by Kid and Koruta-sensei, it's very cute!
The album title is called "DANGEROUS". Yes!
なんでもアイリスをつければいいって問題じゃないかもしれないけど、ちょうどハマったんでね、DANGEROUSな、とても危険的でホッとなアルバムになってます！
It fit just right, so "DANGEROUS"—a very dangerous and hot album!
Yes, it is written by... I mean there's many songs written by all sorts of songwriters from all over the world!
There are many songs written by all sorts of songwriters from all over the world!
and there's going to be a lot of Eurobeat songs, but also songs that are not Eurobeat as well,
new genres as well. So, I hope you guys look forward to that.
あの国内外の様々なクリエイターにユーロビート以外の楽曲も多数作ってもらってます
Creators from both Japan and abroad have created many songs other than Eurobeat for us!
and I will be performing, of course, performing one of the signs for you today!
And I will be performing, of course, performing one of the songs for you today!
今日もね、あの1曲披露しようかなと思ってます。
Today, I'm planning to reveal one song.
その曲はね、あのユーロビートサークルサウンドホリックさん
The song I'm going to sing for you today was written and arranged by the Eurobeat circle, Sound Holic!
yes, they're very famous for Eurobeat.
I'm really glad, I'm really happy to be able to work with them, thank you so much.
今回のあの、披露する楽曲は作曲編曲国内のユーロビートを得意とするクリエイターさん、サウンドホリックさんでございます。
The song being revealed this time was composed, arranged, and produced by Sound Holic, who specialize in domestic and international Eurobeat!
新たなユーロビートの見せ方になると思うんで、楽しみにしてて。
Since it will be showing a new side of Eurobeat, I'm really looking forward to it.
It's Eurobeat, but there's something about it that's also not very Eurobeat, so I hope you guys know what I mean when I sing it.
It is Eurobeat, but there's something about it that's also not very Eurobeat, so I hope you guys know what I mean when I sing it.
the digital release will be happening on 12 AM JST, the upcoming 12 AM JST after this, so make sure you stream it on Spotify and other streaming services, yeah!
The digital release will be happening at 12 AM JST, the upcoming 12 AM JST after this, so make sure you stream it on Spotify and other streaming services, yeah!
この後ね、ええとデジタルリリースも各配信サイトで行われます。ええと、0時に配信されます。楽しみにしててね。
After this, the digital release will also be held on various streaming sites starting at 12:00 AM, so please look forward to it!
すごいド派手な曲です。楽しみだ。And as for the details of the album, I will be talking about that at the very end of this live.
It's a very flashy song, I'm excited. And as for the details of the album, I will be talking about that at the very end of this live.
アドリブの生放送はこの後最後のほうでね、色いろ説明しちゃうんで、最後まで見てね。
For the rest of the livestream, I'll be explaining various things at the very end, so be sure to watch until the end!
All right then, please listen to my new song, BE MY FLAME! 新しい曲聞いてください、BE MY FLAME!
All right then, please listen to my new song, "BE MY FLAME"! Please listen to the new song, "BE MY FLAME"!
(Blazin' fire)
(Blazing fire)
Can't control it anymore, I'm burnin' up red
Crazy thoughts fillin' my head
(Tension rising to the top,)
(Won't look back, I'll never stop,)
(Blazing, boiling, gettin' hot,)
(It's your fault, baby)
Fever burning up inside, It can't be contained
Got my heart goin' up in flames
Tell me you can feel the searing heat
(Come on and come on, I wanna confess, Baby, oh baby, I'm gettin' obsessed)
Are you gonna run away, or burn up with me?
(Crank it up, crank it up, hotter and hotter, Gonna be, wanna be ready for more)
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough,
Fanning the flame of love (And now it's taking over)
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever,
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
(Blazin' fire)
I'm gonna wanna turn it up, I'm burnin' up, can't get enough
Maybe I'm too hot to touch, It's your fault, baby
I can't hide it anymore, I'm bearing my soul,
Let these flames swallow me whole
This is how we're gonna play; A dangerous game,
Got your fire runnin' through my veins
Baby, can't you read between the lines?
(Look at me, look at me turnin' to ash, breakin' me shakin' me makin' me crash)
Gonna sear it all away until you're mine
(Drivin' me drivin' me drivin' me crazy, tellin' me tellin' me what do you mean)
I'm caught in a heat wave, I'll never get enough,
Fanning the flame of love (And now it's taking over)
Blazin' fire, make me a believer,
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air.
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever,
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
I'm only getting started...
Blazin' fire, show me your illusion
It doesn't matter if it's real or a dream
Wild desire, fueling my delusion
I want you burning for me!
Blazin' fire, make me a believer
I'm gettin' dizzy from the smoke in the air
Wild desire, burnin' like a fever
Come hold me close if you dare!
Fire lover, be my flame
Keep me burning
Fire lover, call my name
Sweet love burn me away
So, how did you guys like my birthday 3D live?
We had so much going on from the new 3D outfit debut, new merch, to my first album announcement, solo live announcement, and new song performances!
We had so much going on from the new 3D outfit debut,
new merch, to my first album announcement, solo live announcement, and new song performances!
I think it was packed with so much, so I'd like to give you guys a recap and share the details.
I think it was packed with so much, so I'd like to give
you guys a recap and share the details.
ライブ本編どうでしたか？いろいろとね、告知盛りだくさんだったと思うので、改めておさらいと詳細をお伝えします。
How was the live? I'm sure there were tons of announcements,
so let's go over the recap and details again.
まずはグッズから！First up, the merch!
First up, the merch!
We have the Acrylic Diorama StandRyS illustrated by Unouno Piske sensei, the ChibiRyS Tote Bag illustrated by Lian sensei, the Race QueenRyS Keychain, which is a really cute race queen plushie keychain, and the YabaiRyS pouch!
We have the Acrylic Diorama StandRyS illustrated by Unouno Piske-sensei,
the ChibiRyS Tote Bag illustrated by Lian-sensei, the Race QueenRyS Keychain,
which is a really cute race queen plushie keychain, and the YabaiRyS pouch!
For full set bonuses, the limited edition includes a postcard with a handwritten message and a foil stamped autograph. The standard version includes a postcard with both a foil stamped message and autograph. And the sales will start at 1:15 pm, which is like real soon, if not maybe even now.
For full set bonuses, the limited edition includes a postcard with a handwritten message
and a foil-stamped autograph. The standard version includes a postcard with both a foil-stamped
message and autograph. And the sales will start at 1:15 p.m., which is like real soon,
if not maybe even now.
フルセットをご購入いただいた方には、数量限定版は直筆メッセージ＆箔押し複製サイン入りポストカードがついてきます。通常バージョンは箔押し複製サイン＆メッセージ入りポストカードになります。この後1時15分にカートオープンするよ！もうすぐだよ！
For those who purchase the full set, the limited edition comes with a postcard
featuring a handwritten message and foil-stamped duplicate signature. The standard version
comes with a postcard featuring a foil-stamped duplicate signature and message.
Cart opening is at 1:15! It's super soon!
続いてアルバムです！Next up the album! This time it's being released in two formats, the CD and vinyl, woohoo! Pre-orders will begin also at 1:15 p.m. JST at the Hololive Production Official Shop, like real soon. As for digital releases, that will happen on July 12th.
Next up, the album! This time it's being released in two formats,
CD and vinyl, woohoo! Pre-orders will also begin at 1:15 p.m. JST at the Hololive Production
Official Shop, real soon. As for digital releases, that will happen on July 12th.
今回はCDとレコードの2種類のリリースとなっておりまして、この後1時15分よりホロライブオフィシャルショップにて予約が開始されます。デジタルリリースは7月12日です。
This time, releases will be available in two formats: CD and record.
Reservations will start at 1:15 PM at the Hololive Official Shop. The digital release is on July 12th.
CDにはここでしか聞けないGravityのリアレンジバージョンとステッカー2種類。レコードにはジャケットとアナバージョンプリントされたLPサイズ両面ポスターカードがついてきます。
The CD includes an exclusive arrangement of "Gravity" heard only here and two types of stickers.
The record comes with an LP-sized double-sided poster card featuring the jacket and another version printed.
ポスターカードじゃないよ！ポスターカード！もっとデカいです。さらにこちらのポスターカードには、両面のどちらかに必ず直筆サインが入ります！サインされる面はランダムでございます。裏面かもしれないし、表面かもしれません。
Not a postcard! A poster card! It's much bigger.
Furthermore, these poster cards will definitely feature a handwritten signature on one of the two sides!
The signed side is random. It could be the back or the front.
CD will include an exclusive rearranged version of "Gravity" and two types of stickers, while the vinyl comes with a double-sided LP-sized poster card. Yes, a pretty darn big poster card, featuring both the main and alternate album covers. Plus, yes a big plus, one side of this poster card will definitely feature a handwritten autograph! The signed side will be random, so it could be on either the alternate jacket side or the main album cover. We'll see when you get it!
CD will include an exclusive rearranged version of "Gravity" and two types of stickers,
while the vinyl comes with a double-sided LP-sized poster card. Yes, a pretty darn big poster card,
featuring both the main and alternate album covers. Plus, yes a big plus, one side of this poster card
will definitely feature a handwritten autograph! The signed side will be random, so it could be
on either the alternate jacket side or the main album cover. We'll see when you get it!
And "BE MY FLAME", which has performed in today's 3D live, will also be digitally released at midnight today, so don't forget to check it out! そしてライブでもお披露目した「BE MY FLAME」は24時にデジタルリリースもあるので、忘れずにチェックしてね！
And "BE MY FLAME", which is performed in today's 3D live, will also be digitally released
at midnight today, so don't forget to check it out! And "BE MY FLAME", which was debuted in the live,
will also have a digital release at midnight, so don't forget to check it out!
And there's more! That's right, my first solo live concert, woohoo! The venue will be in...
Tokyo is at SGC Hall Ariake! Woo!
And it will be held on a Tuesday, on October 6th.
And it will be held on a Tuesday,
on October 6th.
I'm super, super, super excited for this,
and I'm so glad I've got to finally announce it,
and I'm so glad I got to finally announce it,
so I hope you guys will be really excited for it as well, yay!
so I hope you guys will be really excited too, yay!
あとね、えっとソロライブも決まりました！場所は東京SGCホール有明でございます。
And also, a solo live has been decided!
The venue is Tokyo SGC Hall Ariake.
えっと、開催される日程は10月6日火曜日です。
Um, the scheduled date for the event
is Tuesday, October 6th.
すごく楽しみにしてるし、
I'm looking forward to it so much,
もうとにかく、もうこんなライブができる機会自体が本当にまさかできると思ってなくて、とってもワクワクしてますし、
and I never thought an opportunity
for a live like this would actually happen,
これからも準備頑張ります！
so I'll keep working hard to prepare!
Please look forward to further details and information in the future!
Please look forward to further details
and information in the future!
Last but not least, there will be a members only part starting at 1:30 PM pretty soon,
Last but not least, there will be a
members-only part starting at 1:30 PM,
so please come check it out if you can, and join the family.
so please come check it out if you can,
and join the family.
最後にメインゲームパートが1時半から始まるので、よかったらメンバーに入ってみに来てね。
Lastly, the main game part starts at 1:30,
so please join as a member and check it out!
では、ありがとうございました！
Well then, thank you very much!
Thank you very much! IRyS, for now, until the members part.
Thank you very much!
IRyS, for now, until the members part.